https://sterlingcollege.edu/policies/

Policies: Privacy, Security, Refund and Shipping
Sterling College » Policies: Privacy, Security, Refund and Shipping
PRIVACY POLICY
Sterling College respects and is committed to protecting your privacy. We may collect personally identifiable information when you visit our site. We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page(s) you visited. Please be assured that Sterling College will not sell your personally identifiable information to anyone.
SECURITY POLICY
Your payment and personal information is safe when used on the Sterling College website. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read over the internet.
REFUND POLICY
No refunds are provided for application deposits and this policy does not apply to other payments made to Sterling College using a credit card.
All refunds for merchandise purchases from the Sterling College website will be provided as a credit to the credit card used at the time of purchase within five (5) business days upon receipt of the returned merchandise. No refunds are accepted after 30 days of sale.
SHIPPING POLICY
Your merchandise items will ship out within 5 to 7 days of purchase. We determine the most efficient shipping carrier for your order. The carriers that may be used are: U.S. Postal Service (USPS), United Parcel Service (UPS) or FedEx. If you’re trying to estimate when a package will be delivered, please note the following: Credit card authorization and verification must be received prior to processing. Federal Express and UPS deliveries occur Monday through Friday, excluding holidays.
Share It!
Click to share on Facebook (Opens in new window)Click to share on Twitter (Opens in new window)Click to share on LinkedIn (Opens in new window)Click to share on Pinterest (Opens in new window)
Apply
Inquire
Give
Visit
Institutional COVID UpdatesAbout Sterling
At a GlanceMission DrivenOur President
Board of TrusteesBoard of AdvisorsAlumni Association BoardOur LeadershipStrategic InitiativeRian Fried Center Back
AccreditationSterling Timeline Back
Academics
Find your program
EcologyEnvironmental HumanitiesOutdoor EducationSustainable Agriculture & Food SystemsSelf-Designed MajorClimate Justice MinorDraft Animal Power SystemsEducation StudiesNatural History MinorNatural Resources Conservation MinorEnvironmental StewardshipSustainable Sterling Back
FacultyRian Fried CenterThe Foundation of Sterling’s CurriculumCourse CatalogAcademic CalendarGraduation Requirements
The Sterling KitchenThe FarmStudent ActivitiesAthleticsHealth & WellnessResidence Halls Back
Wendell Berry Farming ProgramProfessional Studies
The New American Farmstead Back
Sterling OutcomesAlumni & SupportersParents & FamiliesEmploymentAdmissions and Aid
Apply
Admission RequirementsAdmission DeadlinesTransfer ApplicantsVermontersVeteransHomeschooled ApplicantsInternational ApplicantsVisiting Students Back
InquireExperience Sterling College
Interactive Campus MapOpen HouseFamily WeekendAccommodations Back
DirectionsNews & EventsThe BlogCorporate Foundation and Government RelationsIntranet Back
Apply Now
